I am ready to give life for native hearth,
The spirit of ancestors descendants are famous for,
My land is sacred, My flag flies in the world
A symbol of the great neutral country flies.
The forever great creation of the people!
Native land, sovereign state,
Turkmenistan, light and song of soul,
Long live and prosper for ever and ever!
My nation is united and is veins of tribes
Ancestors’ blood, undying flows,
Storms and misfortunes of times are not dreadful for us,
Let us increase fame and honor!
The forever great creation of the people
Native land, sovereign state,
Turkmenistan, light and song of soul,
Long live and prosper for ever and ever!